{
    "subject": "resource/Jane_Child",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Warner_Bros._Records",
    "human_readable": "Jane Child was recorded by Warner Bros. Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799283742904663,
            "question": "Was Jane Child signed to Warner Bros. Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8910912275314331,
            "question": "Which record label is known for recording Jane Child?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8146964311599731,
            "question": "What record label recorded Jane Child's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7949615120887756,
            "question": "Is Jane Child associated with a particular record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6784337162971497,
            "question": "Who recorded music for Warner Bros. Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6185736060142517,
            "question": "Name a musician recorded by Warner Bros. Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.572826623916626,
            "question": "Who was the artist behind the recordings on Warner Bros. Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5458800792694092,
            "question": "Which artist was signed to Warner Bros. Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.480818510055542,
            "question": "What company released Jane Child's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43599626421928406,
            "question": "What music company released Jane Child's songs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jane Child was recorded by Warner Bros. Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7248_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company released Jane Child's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7248_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which artist was signed to Warner Bros. Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7248_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the artist behind the recordings on Warner Bros. Records?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7248_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7248_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Jane Child's album \"Jane Child\" and single \"Welcome to the Real World\" were released under Warner Brothers Records, supporting the statement that Jane Child was recorded by Warner Bros. Records."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}